hooniverse.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy | Hooniverse

**Hooniverse Privacy Statement**  
What follows is the Privacy Statement for Hooniverse (Hooniverse.com).

Please read this statement regarding and if you have questions please feel free to email us at [Admin@Hooniverse.com](mailto:admin@hooniverse.com).

 **Email Addresses  
**You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our [Admin@Hooniverse.com](mailto:admin@hooniverse.com).

 **Ownership of Information  
**Hooniverse is the sole owner of any information collected on our website.  
**  
Comments/Message Boards  
**If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use a comment validation system in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

 **Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies  
**Hooniverse may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to manage users’ site preferences and ensure the site’s functionality. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our website is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

 **Third Party Cookies  
**Hooniverse and its advertisers may also use ad network providers and other service providers to help present customized content and advertisements on the website. These providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their content and advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience. Hooniverse may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as a Hooniverse reader (such as user age and zip code) with certain ad network and service providers to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network and content providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not that of Hooniverse. You must check with the specific ad networks and service providers for their specific policies.

 **Traffic Reports  
**Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

 **Legal proceedings  
**We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Hooniverse may need to disclose information when required by law.

 **Links  
**Hooniverse frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our website we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Hooniverse.

 **Notification of Changes  
**When Hooniverse makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

 **Contact Information  
**If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please reach us at [Admin@Hooniverse.com](mailto:admin@hooniverse.com).

Last Updated: 1-12-2010
